my name is MIA Jackson and I'm from
Columbus Georgia Columbus Georgia is a
military town my parents are still there
my sister still there and it was cool
it's close to something say it rule
country ass areas but my favorite things
are where I love old ass good ass gossip
I will read anybody's Wikipedia page and
when I go to the page I'm going straight
to scandals I want to know got a secret
and black baby and while I'm thinking
about it and I'm gossiping but have you
never done a side by side Tom Cruise and
his adopted son they kind of stay in
illness that's that man baby I'm
learning about a year ago was it for
comedy yeah but was it also because my
friend had a room available to rent
absolutely so much comedy in New York is
so much stage time and it's just the
right place to be for stand-up comedy
and I love comedy so I wanna be where
comedy is gonna be here did you tell
them a gigantic black lady can you tell
the people are oh wow just not even nice
about it oh yeah I'm a very giant
lady I'm no no I'm six feet tall and I
have a boyfriend who's six four and okay
there you go look at you being impressed
about a man you don't even know I like
because I am a tall woman I don't have
height privilege because I can't I can't
play fight with this man
I can't wrestle with him like I don't
think you understand if I walk down the
hall with a pillow I'm a legitimate
threat I think I'm being all cute like
and he's like stand down be a
pillow fight not a domestic dispute I
don't know what it's like to ever be the
little spoon cuz I'm just too damn big
for it so when we color we don't spoon
we knife so we're very much like this my
height also is making people think I
have a lot of authority I get a lot of
people asking me questions every day and
I think it's because I'm from the south
and I also have a welcoming bosom so one
day so I am leaving Nordstrom Rack okay
I got a bunch of bags on my hand this
woman runs up to me off the street and
she goes why is the train down I'm sorry
I don't know I don't I don't know I've
been inside and also I'm not wearing a
uniform okay and so I just had this
moment where I had to look at myself and
I was like oh no I have a transit
informational shape the body you're like
oh oh my god I am shaped like a
that knows train schedules and I saw my
titties were better than that
and they're not I have trained titties
so she wouldn't leave you go so I'm
trying to move it she still just kind of
standing here I'm like okay I said are
you going inside or not and she goes oh
I'm going in I said well then you need
to stand clear of the closing doors bye
guys
[Applause]
[Music]